It's a little...
Is it coming up here?
Am I in the shot?
Am I standing?
No, it hasn't started.
I know some of you have started, but...
It hasn't started.
No, it hasn't started.
Little by little, as they come this way.
Let's get off.
Oh, but you don't have to move.
Okay, okay.
I think it's okay.
It's started.
It started suddenly.
Oh!
LOL!
Fail.
Well then, hello everyone.
Let's see, so what's the delivery of this, now.
This is something that.
The National Never Lose Tour.
It's safe.
Yes, the invidetoxes, please take care of them.
Please do.
Here we go.
The National Never Lose Tour Review is now available.
It has begun.
Thank you all for watching.
Thank you very much.
You've been out of work for the last couple of weeks?
Is it over already?
Oh, it's already Saturday and Sunday.
Good night.
A week before the middle of the year,
I see.
You're at Selfridge's, right?
We're in the middle of it.
I think it's done.
We started at 5:00, and we're about 70% through.
We're in the middle of a shower.
Maybe they're previewing.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's 370, but everyone is tweeting now and asking me to bring it here.
430 people.
Oh, really?
Oh, 457.
The number is increasing.
Thank you very much.
I'm very happy.
But I feel like it's been a long time since I've been on tour. And him, too.
That's for sure.
It feels like we've been doing it for about a year now.
That's about right.
Well, we're doing it.
The National Never Lose Tour started in March.
21 volumes in total.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Cheers.
Everyone's crying.
How do I watch this?
You're watching the feed, right?
What do you mean?
You watch the feed, right?
No, no, no. We talk about it.
Talk?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow, that's a long story.
No, no, no, no.
We have a lot to talk about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I've been around a lot, haven't I?
Looking back, the first one was Sendai, Kanagawa, Hyogo, Osaka, Aichi, Chiba, Saitama, Hyogo, Hiroshima, Wakado, Tokyo, and Tokyo only.
That's amazing.
It's a long way around.
It felt like a long time.
Yes, it's been about 3 months.
It was only one week, but it was long.
Yes, it was.
You have to have a lot of mental strength to do this.
It's amazing.
Yes, it is.
The last tour was pretty amazing, wasn't it?
It was the first tour, so it was staged.
I wasn't sure if I could do it.
Sometimes.
It was your first time.
That's right.
It was fun.
Tohoku-san is famous for changing his enlightenment.
We have changed songs between the first and second parts of the concert.
He changed some songs in the first and second sessions.
But this time, we decided to change almost nothing,
I think you might not get bored from the first rehearsal.At first, you might not get bored from the rehearsal.
We are going to Sendai, aren't we?
Again and again, right?
That's right.
I was worried about that at the rehearsal stage, too.
But I don't think I got tired of it, I think I pursued it more and more.
That's right.
It was frustrating.
The environment was totally different from place to place, and the way of doing things changed.
The atmosphere was different.
It was different.
That's right.
There were aspects of growth that we didn't realize,
Jemin told me that everyone has grown,
I'm glad we did it.
It was good.
More than anything.
You also moved the boxes and so on.
That's right.
It was amazing, wasn't it?
It was heavy, wasn't it?
Heavy.
It was heavy.
I really wondered if it would be okay during rehearsal.
I'm going to move it.
I'm going home.
Running.
I thought someone would get caught.
That's right.
Someone moved between the two.
Really.
That's right.
That was amazing.
And he's so reluctant to do it on the set,
I really don't know.
Someone was shouting.
So, Ban-chan.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
I don't know.
Oh no, I can't move.
You know, we were practicing like an old lady's "karakara" until the very last minute at rehearsal.
It was so dry.
But on the day of the show, a big one showed up,
It was great. Everyone did a great job.
You did a great job.
That's great.
We did it.
You got to see it.
The number of eyes was incredible.
Oh, man.
I could see them.
I could see.
That's amazing.
Yes, I could see it from Makinoyasan's personal engine.
It's amazing.
I want you to see it. It's so real.
It's like an idol's reality.
It's really bad.
I took a picture of that part,
I wanted to take a picture of that part and give it somewhere.
I can't do that anymore.
I wanted to give it away.
I know, right?
In the dark, you know? Like that.
Like a star.
Yes, it's true.
It's beautifully done.
They're stable and that color.
What are we going to do, look back one by one, one yen at a time?
No, but if we do that, first of all,
I'm afraid we'll lose every single one.
I'm fine with it like this.
Do you want to look back at the set list?
Great.
I love Bamiley.
Why?
Is that okay?
I like Bamiley's story.
It's something that's been key this year,
I haven't told you about.
Like Sendai.
What?
What was that?
You don't have to tell me.
About how hard it was...
But you should decide whether you want to tell us or not.
I don't care how much.
You don't mind?
What? What?
What?
It's real.
You don't have to be so graphic.
Yes, it does.
Fairy tale.
Fairy tale.To the fairy tale.
I get it. I'm good at it.
I'm curious.
On the painful first day in Sendai Park,
The day before?
The day before.
The day before,
I had a fever.
The next day.
The first day of the tour...
I was pretty...
Um...
You know...
Fluffy.
I didn't have a fever at the time.
I was off.
I'm fluffy now.
That's weird.
I don't know. Thanks. I'm fine.
Yes, you are.
So I just get that fever the day before.
Oh, he said it's over.
Oh, I see.
I was, and Rune-chan was, too.
We were all pretty tired already.
Our schedules were kind of packed.
I don't know if it's okay to say that.
I can't lose.
MV.
Oh, I get it.
The day before the show was the day before the music video shoot.
It's so cold.
It was so cold.
And cold from morning till night.
I have a red nose.
What do you mean?
I'm trying to look cool, but...
My nose is so red!
You all look cold.
Lie here.
And cold.
And we're all burning our meat.
The next day at rehearsal, we were all going to work so hard.
Everybody was dead.
And we had three stoves.
Three stoves stopped.
Three of them stopped.
They stopped for a second.
Summer came.
Tell them Rune-san was sleeping.
We can't go out tomorrow.
If it was just a show, we could cover it.
But the box is impossible.
Like, "What are we going to do?
He said, "The box is impossible.
They've already postponed and canceled the tour.
I can't do it either.
I was like, "I can't do it.
But I got over it.
Thank you.
You did a great job with the buckets.
It's two shows.
Two shows is pretty tough.
Maybe we should move it.
I wish I could have done it.
I enjoyed it.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming to move the box.
You called me.
I'm going to go move some boxes.
You said you would.
It's okay. It's okay.
I knew I could do it.
I'm gonna move the box. I'm gonna move the box.
Not because I'm going to the show, but because I'm going to move the box.
But I also have a favor to ask of you in terms of the content, and I was thinking that I just want you to move the box.
The box is good, so I can do it only when I move the box.
And with Mr. Haneda, too.
Thank you, Lun-chan!
Lun-chan, you're so good.
I know.
Thank you.
Many other things happened, too, right?
Yes, we did.
I got a sore throat.
And it was on my birthday.
I got parched.
My bedclothes were not in good shape.
I know, right?
I did my best.
Yeah, I know.
Group Lion is fun.
Everybody's funny.
It was fun.
I read it out loud.
Is it okay?You sure?
I'll give you a yurascussho.
You, too, Mr. Yura.
If you're not looking for a group...
If you don't want to find a group, you can just search for one.
That's right.
You'll find a lot of groups if you search.
I'm sorry.
Let's make one.
Let me see.
There's a lot of stuff here.
Is this a good place to start?
Where?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
Here.
I'm sorry I bothered you.
I'm sorry about something.
I'm sorry about everyone.
I'll see you early in the morning.
Sleep well, Myu, and show us your beautiful smile again.
So this is it.
I guess this is the series I'm showing you.
There are more.
This is the most recent one.
This one.
No, no, no.
That's it.
If you say sorry, Myu, take a good rest and show us your beautiful dancing again.
Yuna, show us your beautiful smile again.
Waka, let me hear your beautiful song again.
Rine, let me hear your beautiful words again.
Jyu, let's hear your beautiful conversation again.
Mon-chan, watch my beautiful neck again.
Hikaru, watch over my beautiful life again
Ka-ya, look at my pumpkin again
This is the best!
I'm going to die
Everyone did their best
Thank you so much!
I feel better now.
I figured since everyone else was doing it, I should do it.
I came up with the pumpkin face.
It was the last one, and I was out of ideas.
It came to you, didn't it?
It came to me.
It was funny.
That's cheered me up.
Thank you. Thank you.
You made me laugh.
Oh, yeah.
Here's the funny part.
Everyone does that, of course.
I'm sure that's how he really feels about us.
We were like, "Oh, we're not that into it.
He was like, "You don't have to do that.
So we just casually
We were just messing around.
Thank you.
You were nice.
It's really funny.
Did you hear his heated comment?
Oh!
I want to read the one about the idol.
I want to read it.
I want to read it in his own words.
I'm sure you're right.
Not this one.
You want to read this? Him.
That's fine.
Read it.
He can't do that.
It's so long, it takes three scrolls.
You can't read it?
Is that what you really want?
It's fine.
That really stuck out to me.
Are you confident?
I'll read it.
It'll take me about five minutes.
It won't take that long.
One more time.
Classic dance.
I did the sparkle, sparkle, sparkle.
Christmas
Thank you.
Please
Live! Live!
It was really good.
It was great! Thank you!
I have to admit, I'm not here.
I got a call from an unknown number.
What? Who is it?
Why don't you answer it?
What? Are you sure?
No, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.Oh, it's off.
What? Did the client get my phone number?
I'm scared. I'm done.
All right.
I'm going.
Thanks for your help.
To be honest, seeing how far away I am without you...
I don't know if it's okay to look at it.
I wasn't sure if it would ruin my feelings if I saw it.
I was not without anxiety.
But after a good live performance with Match
I thought it would be better if I wasn't there.
They threw away the screws.
I could feel how hard everyone was working.
I could really feel the passion of the audience through the streaming.
I was really touched.
It was a great relief to me.
It was amazing.
The back was great, too.
The way you guys adapted to all the different songs
It's amazing!
It's so much fun to watch when you can change the mood of a song
it's a lot of fun to watch.
The songs were different.
Mr. Far Away.
I heard that everyone was united in their feelings
It's so much stronger than usual.
Even the choreography was more detailed.
Like, a little less here and a little more there.
We have to have the same mood.
or the same interpretation of a song.
I thought I could be a monster if I could switch between the two
I thought I'd be a monster.
I'm still pretty amazing.
I'd be a badass if I mastered it.
Maybe... it's not something you can do normally.
This...
We all have a range of songs.
The ability to adapt is what makes it possible.
I think it's something you can show
I think it's something we can aim for.
I think that's what the staff said to me on the tour.
I really understood what the staff was saying to me on the tour.
It was great to see the level of improvement.
Everything was great.
Everything was really good.
Thank you so much for the parenthood!
It was so good!
I thought, "Only Mr. Far is going to win.
He was also... you know, when I'm the one doing the work, I'm often worried about a lot of things, but...
But you're so much more than everyone thinks you are.
He's really amazing.
I couldn't believe that such a great group was not up there.
It was a great show!
I hope we can aim even higher with everyone on the tour.
I wish him all the best on the tour!
Thank you so much for a great show, it was very moving.
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
I'm embarrassed.
Self's being honest.
No, thank you.
All right, all right, all right.
Everyone's crying.
I'm already crying.
I'm so embarrassed.
It's hot. It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot in this room.
Hearts.
He was sending so many hearts.
Un-chan burst out laughing.
For a second...
I was so moved.
Thank you very much.
Here's a round of applause.
You saved me a lot.
Thank you very much.
I feel so strong.
That's great.
That line.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Hey, guys.
What do you want to buy this for?
It's on.
It's happening.
Oh, my God!
Set
Settlement
Repeat the main part
I think it's okay to use the last
Rust
LastLast
Settlement Announcement
Ta-da!
Can you say first block?
Yes.
All of it?
Flowers.
Bernie.
Sparrow.
This way and that way.
Bad abbreviation
MC
Chiquina
Mr. President
Action
LYANT
FIRE
Meta Hammer
Arisalet
Symphony
Lovely's
Beaster
Musubi
MC Deliberate and Azao Promotion
Tenichi Tateki MC
Bubble Peeling Midnight Express Losing Yata
Uncode de Shinwa to
Oh!
That's great!
25?
Twenty-four.
Twenty-four!
Oh, man!
Isn't it usually 15 or something? Usually?
Yes, well, if it's a one-man show or something big, it's more like 24.
But this one was really long for me.
Yes, it was long. I usually play for 19 minutes, but it was about 2 hours.
Wow.
You danced for almost 2 hours.
Because that 40 minutes there...
What? Where did he go?
Forty minutes.
Medley?
Medley.
That medley lasted 40 minutes?
That long?
Wow, I don't feel it.
Kibakee was the highlight.
Oh, my!
You kinda put me off about the gakki-bakki.
He says it's my favorite part.
Thank you. Thank you for remembering.
I'm glad you remember.
And, um, which one do you want me to do?
It's really easy to talk to you because you change the titles and stuff.
Originally it was
Dokokko kokoro my future
Oh, I see...
Dottokokokko Dosupe...
Well, we started doing our own calls in the middle of the song.
Right, before the end
Yes, before the fall
It's like this...
We had a very fun time.
As a group of people
Before the final call
That's right.
We were just talking about it in the groove.
And we decided on this one.
Seino
Bakki-Bakki-Bakki-Bakki-Bakki-Bakki-Bakki
That's right.
That's it!
Still, the stock won't fall out
rock, paper, scissors!
Yes!
I don't know what's going on here...
I want you all to call.
I want you to say it!
It's so loud and so groovy!
I can't get out of it!
Then he's going to have a good night, isn't he?
He's going to run away, isn't he?
That's why.
I'm still stuck on camera.
That's good.
Big camera.
We decided on the Maginoli, didn't we?
At first, I was a little nervous.
I thought about the sparkles.
And then I thought, "Crackle!
I left it behind.
Ahhh...
I know, right?
Sparkles
I missed it.
Call itTry calling.
You've learned to speak up, too.
Recently from Hokkaido
How was Hokkaido?
Hokkaido
They took my grandma.
When we did that first flower show, I'd never done a flower show with call ants before.
So when everyone imagines the call
Hana! Hana!
So I definitely don't want you to do that.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'll definitely stop.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, man.
I missed that.
I'm sorry about that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't do it, don't do it, don't do it, don't do it.
It's tough.
But, you know, in Hokkaido... part of Hokkaido... or part of Hokkaido... or part of Hokkaido...
There were a lot of calls.
There were calls that weren't said.
I'm sure there were.
But I just had to say it.
I don't know, there were calls that I didn't want to make.
You were saying things you shouldn't have.
Yeah, it's frustrating.
So, for the first time in a long time, everyone was tired after the first part of the show.
Now we're going to the second part.
You know, they've already taken everything from us today.
But I knew it. It's been a long time since I've heard that.
Thank you very much.
I forgot everything.
I know.
I love it.
It's always on, isn't it?
It was great.
I've had so many people tell me how great it was.
Thank you very much.
You don't really see that.
But usually the performers only say thank you for seeing us.
but it's rare to hear a thank you from the audience.
That's for sure.
And you know what else he said?
It's nice, isn't it?
At the finals...
There were a lot of production staff there, you know.
Usually, after the show, everyone just goes home.
But they came to Tohoku-san's side.
Thank you very much to the production staff.
I don't know...
It's like they're saying it to us.
It's like he's trying to be us.
I was so happy that he said that.
Oh, my God...
Everyone!
That's amazing.
That's amazing!
That made me so happy.
I was so happy.
Number 10.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's great.
Oh, wait.
Everybody grows up.
That's great.
I'll take one of them.
Thank you very much.
It's so nice to have it separately.
It's nice to have a separate one, isn't it?
I'm glad.
I'd like to learn more about the culture.
I'd like to learn more about it.
Cultural contents
That kind of thing.
When I hear about it in a totally different place
I feel really proud.
Proud
That's great!
Amazing
You're so kind
You're a good person
You're a good man
You're a good person.
Well, next time you're around nice people.
I'll have them go through the lie detector.
Who the hell isn't lying?
Go through the machine.
Tell me you're not lying.
Go through it.
If it turns red...
I'm not going in.
It's hard.
I can't leaveI couldn't stay away.
You don't seem like a nice guy.
Seems like there aren't many.
And that's that.
They hate me
They hate me.
We've got new songs.
Five new songs.
That's true.
I like it.
Yeah, it's good.
It's gonna be great.
I like it.
You know, the order of the performances has changed a lot.
At the beginning.
That's true.
That's right.
I didn't know it was in the first corner.
I didn't know that.
I didn't know that before we got the idea.
I didn't know.
I mean, I knew.
I don't know.
Nobody knows.
That thing in the production changed things, didn't it?
That's right.
When to pull over.
I didn't know that.
That's right.
If you look at the one at the knot.
Wakuyobi in February
That's right.
It came out before Japan.
That's for sure.
Right?
Yeah. - Yeah.
That's right.
Let's tie the knot.
Let's tie it.
Knots.
Well done.
Two.
I didn't do two.
Knot.
Oh, what was it, a thousand times?
A thousand.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, I don't know, it wasn't really the first performance.
It was like a line connecting us all.
But it ended up being a knot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was just a bunch of lines.
What?
Why?
It's a quest.
But, you know, the lines? The number of lines?
Number of lines.
That's the part where it changes and you get all woozy.
I know, I know, I know.
The intro suddenly goes "wow".
Do you understand? Do you get it?
It's like, "Oh, my God!
I totally get it. I get it.
I like the intromajig of the lines.
No, it looks super fun.
The line intro magic is good.
Before that, it's pretty good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know what I mean?
You know, this...
Your expression changes a lot, doesn't it?
Yeah, they do a lot of things to you.
You know what I mean?
He's very empathetic.
Yes, but...
This unyielding block... It's pretty cool.
I'm not an artist.
I'm not an artist, but... they've got us so tight, you know?
We have to show them
With a line and a whirl
Hwoar!
You know what I mean? It's so obvious.
It's nice.
You know what I mean? The lines give it a little more of a live feel.
Oh, yeah.
I like that.
It gives it a live feel.
The moment when it changes from a show to a live performance.
I get it.
You get it.
That's why I loved the line.
You said that.
It was a lot of work to put this together.This was a lot of work to plan.
Oh, really?
Did anyone else not get it?
No, I'm pretty sure everyone did something.
Yeah, I'm sure I'm forgetting something.
Sounds like Hajime.
Hey, Hajime Hina.
I wonder when it happened.
I don't know how many times.
I didn't know how many times.
Hey...
I said it and it hit me.
Hey.
It was fun, wasn't it?
The planning was the same, and then I also loved every Waka no Aori.
And the aori!
We didn't lose.
You never lost.
Thank you.
Wow.
I see 21 patterns.
Wow, that's great.
That's for sure.
That's amazing.
But after I finished my previous voice, I ran to the manager, to the captain, and asked him what I should do with the aori. I asked him.
Yes, I did.
You said so. You did a great job.
But, you know, it was the last part, so even if you had decided on the story at the beginning, the flow would not change.
Yes, yes, yes.
The bubble is at the end.
Oh, the flow will be changed by the MC and so on.
Yes, when they tell you what you are going to see first.
When you were told first, you know, no, and....
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I see.
What do you do? I was like, "Oh, you told me.
It's just like that.
Yes, it was.
And before that, it was all about his songwriting.
That's right.
Yes, yes, yes.
I thought it would be difficult.
That's right. That's true.
It was interesting, though.
The funniest part was that we were in a battlefield.
Wow!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That was really funny.
Yes, suddenly during the MC, he had to make the flow of "Bubble Poppin", and then he went straight into the song, and he said something like, "This is a battlefield, but....
What did he say?
What was it?
Like, "This is a battlefield.
He said, "This is a battlefield, idols are in a warring age, but this is a battlefield, idols are in a warring age, so this is a battlefield.
Yes, yes, yes.
Cherish every second.
You will all die tomorrow.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm going to die.
Are you crying already?
That's right, that's right.
So you can enjoy the moment.
That's right.
So..,
You're saying this all of a sudden.
I'm going to ask you a question on the Insta-questionnaire, because it's Mon-chan's birthday tomorrow,
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hey, hey, hey, stop it.
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
I've been told.
Stop it, stop it.
But..,
Oh, shut up.
It was. It was. It was.
It's like he was saying, life is short.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's so short.
That's why I'm trying to figure out what to do.
That's right.
I think he told me he was going to die.
Yes, yes, yes.
And at the end, I don't remember,
His work sense,
You know, he was so funny,
He really had a great work sense.
That was amazing. That's for sure.
Oh, I see.
That's great.
When we talked about the break-in.
Ah.
How did you know?
Hey.
When I mentioned something like the cost of the Internet,
You know..,
"Wow! Like he was talking about work sense,
I was hoping that he would just keep going.
I was hoping he would just keep going.
That was the one that really brought the machine intelligence to the table.That was the one that really could have taken the machine intelligence.
Yeah. You were good at it.
The head turning.
But really, it was just like Waka said,
I had to go with the flow,
I've never made a decision before.
So you're going to come out on the battlefield?
Wow!
That's amazing.
His face, when he was in despair.
I think so too.
His face is amazing.
It's not so easy, you know,
He didn't push me.
Yes.
Now.
Not now.
I thought he was playing with me.
I thought you didn't know.
I see.
I miss it.
All of them,
I took all of them from a fixed point,
Amorishu, for example,
I miss it.
Oh, my gosh,
He was so good.
And then there was Pearl's favorite illustration.
Aaah!
That was in the general editorial,
Oh, I miss it!
The general editing.
That must have been hard work, too.
I'm sure it is.
No, no, no.
We talked about it a lot, didn't we?
Yes, we did.
We solicited ideas from everyone,
I had a lot to say.
Yes, we did.
But they will listen to anything that can be taken out of the pearls,
So, it's okay to say ayuiyo.
Ah,
I did it.
It's a deal!
One time for sure.
I'll say "ayuu".
You'll get it.
How did it happen?
I'll say "I'll be your friend".
But..,
Personally, I'm number one,
"Do you like red?
I know, I know.
Osaka.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was really bad.
It was pretty bad.
I thought so.
Yes, it was.
Congratulations.
It was pretty good.
You have to try it once in a different sense of pounding or something.
For example?
A roller coaster.
Crikey!
Caw!
That's what they're thinking.
Crikey!
Caw!
Everybody.
I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it.
It's here.
It's a bug.
Interesting.
A roller coaster.
Oh, my gosh!
It's a bug.
Put your hands up.
Interesting.
What else?
A song about not losing?
Yes.
And the song about not losing.
It became that at the end.
That one.
It's a "Gachi-emo" production.
Gachi-emo production.Gachi-emo production.
It was decided from the beginning, wasn't it?
That's right.
From the time we did it as a free show.
And then they did a version of it as a freebie, too.
But we felt that we should keep it.
Also, they asked us if we wanted to do the engine version on the first day of the finals or the second day.
We did. I missed it.
But since the finals were held on both the first and second days, we decided to do it on the first day.
I wonder how it went.
I don't know, but there was something written about it. I think they left it up to you.
No, I think so, too.
I think so, too.
I think I'm leaving it to you, too.
But that engine is not often done on stage.
We always do it on stage before the show, but this was the first time you showed us the whole thing.
That's right.
That's for sure.
I'm going to make it extreme and do it in front of everyone.
Oh, the audience too?
Isn't it bad?
Who is that?
Who is it?
And then he says, "I'm standing right here.
Go!
Cute!
Hanako!
I'll do it while laughing.
Don't say anything.
Oh, because.
But the MVP is Hajiki-chan's Dori Iwata, right?
Oh, Dori Iwata.
That's really popular.
It's okay to put Dori, Hanako.
It's not about humanity.
It's interesting, isn't it?
On the night of the 19th, on the 1st, I was looking up the tour that I would never lose on Egosaste, and I found out that he graduated.
But you were caught off guard by the music that day.
And, you know, I put it in the story.
Then, through the manager, I got pictures of everyone from different staff members.
He said, "If there are days when everyone is taking pictures, you should help them out.
If they were funny, they would say, "Yes, yes, it's funny,
No, no, no, put it over here.
No, that's it.
That's funny. It's not about fixing it, it's funny.
Everyone did.
It was funny.
Episode 2 was funny, too.
I love episode 2.
I can't wait to play the second episode live.
I want to do it at a live house or something.
I want to do it.
But I'm glad you got it. The audience.
I'm sure. They were really satisfied.
It was fun.
I can throw that pillow toss habit.
I think it's coming back.
That one doesn't have to come back at all, maybe for two episodes.
Please let me perform for you guys.
It was amazing. Surreal.
And it's the boy who says it when he comes back, right?
That's amazing.
And you changed it, didn't you?
The first one was displayed on the first day, the costume one.
It went out of shape there, and I had to put the costume on.
I was really embarrassed and I changed.
I don't know why.
Then, on the 8th day, I asked if I could use it for an encore,
So I made a new one, and even changed my face one more time.
At first, I was able to wear the costume,
I threw in $200,
When I came back, I was in a state of shock.
I was like, "Why do I have to go twice? I was like, "Why did you stay both times?
Maybe they just appeared out of nowhere.
It's true.
It's the time of the first doll.
But you know comedy, don't you?
That's amazing. You know what you're talking about.
It sounds like "Lee Waka".
Riwwaka! Lee Waka!
So when it first came on, I thought the song had suddenly started.
I don't know.
I don't listen to it.
It's really different.
Ertama is there, too.
What?
I'm not.
It's true!
That's it, isn't it?
Bento.
Thank you, Ertama.
I'll be tonight.
Thank you very much.
El Tama, you're so tight.
My bento.
It's from rehearsal.
I'm feeling great.
Thank you.
Sukiyaki.Sukiyaki.
It was very expensive.
It was huge.
It was amazing.
The carrots turned into butterflies.
It was cute.
It was delicious.
It's so cute.
Thank you.
The messages and decorations.
I was so happy.
They were displayed at the rehearsal.
Yes, yes, yes.
It cheered me up, didn't it? I knew it.
The people who waited for us.
The so-called "bento box lunches" are amazing!
Sure, it's the first time, right?
I had a huge appetite.
I like it. With everyone.
Yes, it is.
Yeah, thank you very much.
That was fun.
All over the country. You enjoyed it all.
We had a great time.
We did a lot of sightseeing.
We definitely ate a lot of food.
Yes, we did.
We definitely went out to eat.
I wanted to eat so much that I could almost eat.
Sightseeing. We had a great time.
There was one thing in particular that I remember.
Oh, crabs. Oh.
What?
You really don't know? You don't know?
Crab. Kegani.
Are you angry?
What?
No, it's a perfect crime.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
No, no, no.
I heard you. I heard you.
You heard me?
I did.
You were?
You said you'd definitely ask for a frog or something.
Oh, I see.
And he said, "I didn't ask you to do it, so it's OK.
I thought that was great.
I thought it was great.
I was beaten.
I'm a little scared.
I thought, "That's great.
The clerk told me to bring it quietly.
I guess so.
So, yes.
They brought it to me quietly.
They didn't say, "It's crab," but they just said, "This is just the strongest grill.
This is just the strongest roast.
That's right.
It's crab.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
So cute.
It's a crab.
The waitress is also a perfect crime.
Cute.
Strong criminal, strong criminal.
Crab was tight.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's me.
Oh, no, no, no.
I let it go.
Put it down.
But I thought he didn't notice, so after that, on the way home..,
Was your meal expensive today? I asked.
I just noticed.
No, it was a little expensive.
That's why I didn't notice.
Ha-ha-ha.
Don't you look at it? The menu list.
I don't look at it.
You don't?
Not in detail.
You don't look at it, do you?
That's right.
There are too many.
I'm sure it's a little more than your drinking money.
I don't drink.
That's right.
It was good, wasn't it?
It was delicious.
I really wanted to take a lot of pictures.
I had to have a chair.You have to have a chair.
Oh yeah.
I really wanted to take a picture like this with the crab.
That's right.
I was helping the crab.
That was fun too.
It was really delicious.
Anyway, I'd like to give them out to everyone.
With me, with me, with me, with me, with me.
With me, with me, with me, with me.
No, it was fun.
What did we eat?
Mmm.
That was good. You bought a lot of food.
For me, the first thing I tasted on this tour was a very tasty dish,
Fukuoka's Yumeyumedori?
Yumemedori.
What's that?
The chicken curry with curry that we got as a free gift.
It was delicious!
It was so delicious.
Yes, it was.
The seasoned bone-in meat that Mr. Vachon gave me,
I got as a gift from Mr. Vachon.
That was so good.
That was delicious.
Seriously.
It looks delicious.
I'm recommending it to all my friends who come to Fukuoka.
I have a lot of friends.
Hey.
Which one is it?
It's so scary.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm vicious.
Three different points.
It was good.
It was delicious.
Very different.
Oh, you know what?
What are we going to do?
What was that? What was that? Parfait.
Parfait.
Um, we weren't here for the crab incident.
That's right.
That's why I didn't know about it until that stage.
I went to have a parfait by myself during that one
Eh, it was kind of crowded.
I just felt like, if we all had dinner together, we'd be finished in time.
We definitely wanted to go to about three places for a chime parfait.
But all the places we wanted to go took an hour or two.
Oh, I see.
And it was crowded that day.
Wow!
And with Mr. Waokun, and with Mr. Johnny's.
And I don't know what else... there was a game, too...
It was all there.
It was so crowded, everything.
They had all the big venues.
I see.
And it was almost a treasure.
But miraculously, I went to this really fancy café-like place.
I had a complicated parfait.
Complicated parfait.
It was kind of fancy, wasn't it?
It's not simple, that's why.
Like that sweet bamboo house.
I see.
Cherry blossoms, not cherry blossoms.
I had a cherry blossom parfait.
It was really good.
Cherry blossoms are amazing!
I just got 3,000 yen.
Oh!
If you eat four, you get a crab.
That's for sure.
Oh, no!
You're right.
Certainly.
Sure, sure, sure.
But it was really good.
It was good.
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy.
That was great.
It's good.
I went to eat alone.
I'm sorry about that.
But you guys should go eat crab.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was delicious.Delicious.
Sweet.
This was good.
Everyone bought so many souvenirs.
Ah!
I see it.
I bought 14,000 yen.
That's amazing.
I didn't buy 4 souvenirs.
Yeah, but I bought 14,000 yen.
I sent them all to my mom, so...
at home.
I mean, I sent her the salmon and shrimp.
But by the time I got home, they had expired,
So I told her to eat my share,
I bought them. I took care of my parents.
He's so cute.
I'm glad.
You know, even if you buy souvenirs in Hokkaido,
We all went to Tokyo,
And then we went to the tour finale,
And after that, I had to work for a while,
I had to go home with my mom for a while,
I was dead.
So, even if you buy souvenirs, everyone travels on their own.
That's right.
We're all at home, making our own way.
Oh, that's right.
Thank you. Crab sushi.
Crab sushi.
I ate crab sushi.
Hey, it arrived.
And there are people involved, right?
Sukipi.
Sukipi is good.
Tokyo.
I'm glad.
There were a lot of great people there.
It was gorgeous.
Shouldn't we see the people involved?
Almost all of them were related to the event.
The level of people involved was amazing.
I don't like to say "level," but...
I'm glad that so many people came to see the show.
I'm glad that so many people came to see us,
I wondered if they were really interested in us.
I thought they knew of it.
And I wondered if they enjoyed seeing 25 songs.
Maybe it was fun.
But, you know, they genuinely gave us feedback.
I was happy.
I was happy to hear the background music,
Everyone was in charge of the members.
We all did our best.
It's nice, isn't it?
Everyone sang together.
It was fun.
But it was so much fun,
I can still hear it in my head.
I can listen to it at nightfall.
It's a small thing.
Maybe it's just a small thing.
A lot has happened, hasn't it?
Is there anything you'd like to ask?
Gentlemen.
What happened during the brass?
This part of the set list is a mystery.
I don't understand.
There.
Next.
The second one.
Are you curious?
I don't know, I've heard from Mr. Masalon, that's not good, I've heard from Pattin.
Here, here, here, here.
You see that first box?
You know, the first box, we were all banging the cloth in the box.
And Shoreline was doing the "bang".
But you can't see the moment when they're filming.
Oh, wow.
The first one is when the pillows go up.
Yeah, the pillow.
I know it's a pillow, but that's why he thought it was going to be like this.
Oh, wow.
What do you mean?
What? I thought the box was supposed to be like this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I thought it was some kind of trick.
Uh, something like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're chimity.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
3,2,3,4,5,6,7
1,2,3,4,5,6,7
Bang!
You gotta think analog.
Yeah, make it all up.
So that was the lighting.
It's the name of the shrine.
That was amazing.That was amazing.
It was amazing.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, it was.
I didn't really attend the rehearsal at Sendai Pit this time.
I was surprised that it was the first time at Sendai Pit.
What?
I was surprised that it was the first time in Sendai Pit.
I was asked to answer some questions.
Well...
You got a lot of questions.
So, you know, you were really anxious during rehearsal, right?
I was looking at the sensitives, and I was like, "Why are you doing this?
I was so moved by what you showed me.
Really? I'm so happy.
I got a lot of comments like that from the captain after the Sendai show.
We were so relieved because we were so anxious.
I was so relieved.
You can see it from the back in Sendai.
Can I say something? I'm just saying that this was the first time...
The first time.
The first time?
Oh...
Yes.
Like a first time showing.
Yes, it was.
It was like that.
You know, the second day of the Line Cube, I think.
The moment the audience knew we were coming with the final BGM,
I couldn't hear Hina's earpiece on the left side.
Oh yeah, that's right.
We were on standby, and about 5 seconds before the show was about to start,
I was ready, and about 5 seconds before we were about to start, Hina's earpiece on the left side stopped working,
So we had to play the background music one more time and the audience started to listen to it.
Oh, wow....
Tokyo 1st day?
Day 1.
I had played it twice before the baseball game,
I thought they would come at the end, but after playing it one more time,
Oh, no.
Yeah.
Bye,
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
is 〜〜〜〜〜〜.
I was looking forward to it.
You were looking forward to it.
Oh, I see.
After all that, 50 minutes.
Whoa!
What made you cry, Captain?
Huh?
So, between there and
See Saitama.
But..,
It was good.
I'm glad.
Surprisingly, the overall
Saitama.
I didn't really feel
I didn't know.
I thought I'd be pretty pissed off.
Oh, no.
That kind of thing happens a lot.
The person who's doing it and the person who's watching it have completely different impressions of it, don't they?
That's right.
I'm not really feeling it anymore.
The other day...
The song about not losing.
The last one.
I released the live video.
Today's 21st
I'm releasing it intentionally on purpose.
I'm going to release it on purpose on purpose.
Oh, wow!
Do you want to watch it with me?
I see.
Do you want to see it with me?
Do you want to see it the other way around?
That's what I'm talking about.
You're a grown-up, aren't you?
This is Tokyo Fikes.
You're fast.
That's great.
It opens at 9:00 p.m.
Let's see.
You can see it here now.
Thank you for your time.
Okay, penlight.
Certainly.
Don't you have to flap?
Can you see? Everyone.
Do you want to flap it?
A little bit.Just a little.
Just one.
School request.
It's a good thing.
Just a little.
It stings.
May I?
Oh, there's more.
Let's get to it.
Deliberately deliberate expert.
Thank you.
That's great.
I see.
I knew it. Family's up.
It's true.
So cute!
Cute.
Sounds good.
I thought you were shaking.
Cute.
I see it's in your hair, too.
That's amazing.
That's great.
Amazing. You're so cute.
Cute.
So cute.
Where's your camera?
How many cameras did you have?
Twenty-one.
That's amazing.
You're so cute.
Oh, you just winked.
He's winking.
What are you doing?
Now that's fun.
It's so hard.
Babirimisa, you're drunk.
The picture is beautiful.
Kihiyo
Cute
oping
my favorite
hana
me
Cute.
It's cute.
Like a dog.
A dog?
What is it? What is it?
It's not good.
It's not good, is it?
It's beautiful.
It's like when I was a kid,
Yes, it is.
It's cute.
It's nice.
Buttocks.
Cute.
It's cute.
That's it.
It's amazing.
He's sleeping. He's sleeping.
Sleeping... sleeping... sleeping... sleeping...
Three!
Three, three, three!
What? Cute?
Cute!
Gross!
Ha-ha-ha.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Everyone's dancing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So cute!
So cute.
I've been told that, haven't I?
You don't walk here, do you?
They don't walk here.
They won't walk here.
Nerd.
It's really flowing.
You're so cute.
That's great!
Last four!
That's fun.
So we have 21 hours?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm running out of time, so I'll make an announcement.
Announcement?Announcement?
We will do it in 8 minutes.
Announcement?
Announcement time?
Yes, please.
Time?
Yes, let's go.
Please do.
First of all, let's do it.
Eight and 11 minutes.
Wait a minute.
No!
No, no, no.
Then do it, Asahi.
There's nothing wrong with it.
It's not bad.
I'm Kaya.
I've been looking for your idol page. I was.
It's not bad.
Kaya and Seira.
Come over later, when I do this.
Later.
Tuesday, June 4.
Good morning, the meeting is open.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all.
Please come and join us.
Please let me know what you think.
Surely.
Please let us know what you want to tell us.
Yes, I'm sure you are right.
June 4th.
Please let me know.
Soon, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Wait a minute.
I'll put it in words.
On August 11, right?
We will be celebrating our 8th anniversary.
Yay.
It's going to be the 8th anniversary of Suehirogana.
It will be held in Yamagata Prefecture.
Yamagata Prefecture.
Cha-cha-cha-cha.
It's been a long time.
Oh, I see.
Recently, except for Sendai, we've been doing everything together.
I see.
I'll go from home.
I want to go.
Can I go?
Please come to a stop.
It's going to break.
It's gonna break.
It's gonna break. Just a little more of that.
One time for all of you.
It's gonna break.
It's going to break.
I'll break it.
Many juniors were born.
Juniors' Festival.
Juniors' festival.
Ten years difference in Yamagata.
I'm so happy.
We did it.
It's been a long time since we've had a big event among our family members.
That's right.
Please don't expect this kind of thing.
Oh, I see.
That's, that's right.
Still time.
If you want to see something solid,
Come home, juniors.
It's a little bit real.
Oh, yeah.
Sounds real.
Shall we go home?
Like, "Let's go home.
If you put it in a singlestick.
Yes, that's right.
I won't move.
Not moving.
Maybe I won't use the microphone.
Kindness.
I guess so.
Please enjoy.
Yes.Yes.
Is that about right?
I guess.
Yes, it is.
Well, I'll see you at 8:00 p.m.
Yes, that's right.
From 8:00 p.m.
What a surprise.
The announcement of the grand prix for the deliberate bruising championship?
We will have a presentation.
Yay.
You can all look forward to that as well.
Well, thank you very much for today's delivery.
That's all.
Stardust of Ujira Mijilak.
Who wishes a lot to everyone.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Bye bye.
See you.